Kris Labovitch

91 Marion Street, Somerville MA 02143

I am a Salesforce Certified Advanced Administrator, Sales Cloud Consultant, and Platform App Builder, with experience in Java development and a business degree that positions me to solve business problems through building custom Salesforce solutions.

SKILLS/CERTIFICATIONS

cell: 857-231-0309

- Salesforce Certified Advanced Administrator
- Salesforce Certified Sales Cloud Consultant
- Salesforce Certified Platform App Builder
- Salesforce Certified Administrator
- Java/Apex

- Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, Outlook, PowerPoint)
- SQL
- Stata
- Agile Development
- Excellent writing and communication skills

EDUCATION

BRANDEIS UNIVERSITY, WALTHAM, MA

Double Major - Business, Politics

May 2017

Graduated Cum Laude

klabovitch@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

CATCHPOINT SYSTEMS, BOSTON, MA

Aug 2017 - Present

Junior Salesforce Business Analyst

- System Administrator for Salesforce and Clari Platforms
- Provide support to 100+ Salesforce users worldwide and act as a point of contact for end-user support
- Designed/built/documented a sales process to support the target account strategy using Salesforce
- Created advanced formula fields, validation rules, workflows
- Created custom reports and dashboards to track key performance indicators (quota attainment, pipeline management, etc.)

PARENTS HELPING PARENTS, WATERTOWN, MA

Jul 2017 - Present

Salesforce Volunteer

- Conducted requirements workshop for solution design and developed screens and workflow
- · Performed migration of data from excel spreadsheets into Salesforce using Data Loader for ETL functions

HARVARD BUSINESS PUBLISHING, BOSTON, MA

Jun 2016 - Aug 2016

Marketing Intern

- Analyzed data layouts in Salesforce.com to improve overall integrity and organization
- Researched potential leads for marketing campaigns and sales outreach efforts

STRATEGIC MIGRATION, SYDNEY, AUSTRALIA

Oct 2015 - Dec 2015

Migration Associate

- Compiled/processed documentation for visa applications for submission to the Department of Immigration
- Processed client inquiries, filings and assisted on attorneys' case studies

ADVISORY COUNCIL TO BOSNIA AND HERZEGOVINA, WASHINGTON DC

Jun 2015 - Jul 2015

International Fellow

- Lobbied Congress to gain support for anti-genocide resolution
- Drafted press releases and letters on behalf of the organization's initiatives

MFS INVESTMENTS, BOSTON, MA

May 2014 - Aug 2014

Trade Processing Analyst

- Created spreadsheet calculations to validate trades made by investment bankers
- Conducted data reconciliation and automated several of these processes using Excel

LEADERSHIP

NEWTON NORTH HIGH SCHOOL, NEWTON, MA

Sep 2014 - Jun 2017

Assistant Tennis Coach

BRANDEIS: Alpha Delta Phi Literary Fraternity Fundraising Chair, Student Senator, Deis Impact Coordinator